Friends, ICICI LBA has disclosed its quarter three
numbers.  So let's
see what is there
in the numbers of quarter three, the data is basically in lakhs here.
I'm telling you in crossers.
So, if we talk about the last quarter,
in the last quarter the company had
generated a total income of Rs 6582 crore.  Last
year it was around Rs 5882 crore, whereas if you look at it now,
you can see it increasing to Rs 6610 crore.
So if we go year after year, you are seeing
a significant increase in the company's revenue year after year.
You can roughly say that there is a jump of around 12%
in the company's revenue year after
year, whereas if we go on a quarterly basis,
you have seen a slight jump on a quarterly basis.  If you
look here,
you can say there is a slight increase.  There
is a jump of around half a %.  So
you can say it is almost flat on a quarterly basis.  So the company
's total income is flat on quarterly basis.
Whereas it has been seen increasing year after year.   Let us
look at the gross premium return of the company.
So see, in the last quarter the company
generated Rs 758 crore, last year it generated Rs 6474 crore,
whereas if you look at it now, you can see the gross premium of the company
going away to Rs 7432 crore.  So if you
look here, you can
see it increasing year after year, quarter after quarter.
How much of the company has been shown though
?  Gross premium of around Rs 7432 crore has been
shown in this quarter.
Whereas the market estimate was
around Rs 7326 crore.  So if you look here,
you are seeing that the market value is around what it was.  So you can say that the
gross premium is what you are getting
to see inline.  Let us
see what the company's expenses are.
So see, in the last quarter the company had
spent Rs 5830 crore.  5197 crores last year.   If you
look at it now, you can see the company spending Rs 639 crore.
So if you
look at the expenses, you will see that the expenses are a little higher.
Let us
first see what the company's profit would be.
So if you look at the operating profit first, it was Rs
752 crore in the last quarter.  Last year it was Rs 685 crore,
whereas now it is around Rs 571 crore.  So if you
look at operating profit, you
see it falling quarter after quarter for 10 years.
And in such a situation, if we
talk about the net profit of the company, then see,
in the last quarter the net
profit of the company was Rs 819 crore, last year it was around Rs 724 crore,
whereas now you have seen it falling to Rs 658 crore.
So here
you got to see a big surprise
because the profit of the company is
seen falling year after year, if you
look at both year after year and quarter after quarter then
you got to see a decline in the profit of the company,
you got to see a decline of around 10%
year after year whereas the market estimate
was that it can be seen to increase by around 18 to 20%
because the company has shown a
profit of Rs 658 crores whereas the
market estimate was around Rs 777 crores, so if you
look here then
you are seeing the market estimate very low, so you are getting to
see the profit very much below estimate.  Let us
see what is the EPS of the company.  So see, the
EPS of the company in the last quarter was
around ₹16.5, last year it was ₹14.5, if we look at it now it is
around ₹13.  So if you
look at it overall, you have seen the numbers to be a little weak.
Because if
you look at the revenue, the revenue is fine because you have seen as much
premium income of the company as you wanted.  It
is inline.  You can see the
gross premium of the company online.  There
is a significant increase year after year.  But there was a decline in the company's net profit
and operating profit.
Whereas the market felt that
you would see a big jump.  So the
profit is weak.  Revenue is being seen in line.
So if you look at the overall results,
you would say they are a little weak.  Let's see
how the market reacts to this.   If you
like the video then please like it.  Also,
please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you.